A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Second Administration, Series 37.2 FA439A
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Second Administration, Series 37.2
1963-1966
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA439A
120 microform reels 120 microfilm reels.
Scope and Contents
Major subjects contained in the files include:
Administration. Aging. Agriculture. Authorities and Commissions. Banking. Civil Defense. Commemorative Observance. Conservation. Consumers. Correction. Disasters. Discrimination. Education. Executive Clemency. Extradition. Fiscal. Fund raising. Government. Health & Sanitation. Honorary Designation. Horse Racing. Housing. Insurance. Investigations. Invitations. Judiciary. Labor. Law. Legislation. Licensing. Mental Hygiene. Military and Naval. Organizations. Parks and Recreation facilities. Personnel Administration. Politics. Property. Public Safety. Public Utilities. Public Works. Regrets. Resignations and Vacancies. Statements. Transportation. Veterans. Welfare. Youth.
Conditions Governing Access
Microfilm user copies are open for research. The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original paper records is restricted.
Arrangement
Series 37 is arranged into 4 subseries:
Subseries 1: First Administration, 1959-1962. Subseries 2: Second Administration, 1963-1966. Subseries 3: Third Administration, 1967-1970. Subseries 4: Fourth Administration, 1971-1973.
Material is arranged alphabetically by subject within each subseries.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aid for Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Series 37 include:
FA439 Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, First Administration, Series 37.1
FA439B Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Third Administration, Series 37.3
FA439C Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Fourth Administration, Series 37.4
- Second Administration, 1963-1966; 2; 120 microform reels
  Scope and Contents
  The following microfilm reels do not exist: Reel 47, Reel 80, Reel 114, Reel 115 and Reel 116.
  - Administration (Reel 1, Reel 2, Reel 3)
    - Executive Chamber (Reel 1, Reel 2, Reel 3)
      - Equipment (Reel 1, Frame 11)
        - Governor's Car (Reel 1, Frame 13)
      - Governor's Itinerary (Reel 1, Frame 18)
      - Interoffice Memos (Reel 1)
        - Alexander Aldrich (Reel 1, Frame 73)
        - Edith Baike (Reel 1, Frame 80)
        - Earl Kent (Reel 1, Frame 81)
        - Alton G. Marshall (Reel 1, Frame 83)
        - Robert L. McManus (Reel 1, Frame 89)
        - Charles H. Palmer (Reel 1, Frame 116)
        - Dr. Ronan (Reel 1, Frame 119)
        - Isabelle Savell (Reel 1, Frame 136)
        - W.A. Sharkey (Reel 1, Frame 141)
        - Elt Van Ness (Reel 1, Frame 143)
        - Raymond Wickham (Reel 1, Frame 144)
        - R.A. Wiebe (Reel 1, Frame 147)
      - Memos (Reel 1)
        - Anderson - Murray (Reel 1, Frame 150)
        - Osterman - Wright, 1966 November 9-December (Reel 1, Frame 169)
      - Mail Report
        - 1966 November 9-December (Reel 1, Frame 185)
        - 1963 January-1964 November 9 (Reel 2, Frame 6)
      - Office Space, New York City (Reel 2, Frame 63)
        - Personnel (Reel 2, Frame 64)
        - Press Conference (Reel 2, Frame 84)
        - Records (Reel 2, Frame 98)
        - Inauguration (Reel 2, Frame 109)
        - General (Reel 2, Frame 127)
      - Executive Mansion (Reel 2, Frame 140)
      - General (Reel 2, Frame 226)
        - Trips
          - 1966 April-November (Reel 2, Frame 238)
          - 1963 January-1966 May (Reel 3, Frame 5)
      - General (Reel 3, Frame 34)
      - Department of State (Reel 3, Frame 103)
  - Aging, Subject (Reel 3, Reel 4)
    - Problems of
      - Employment (Reel 3, Frame 148)
      - Governor's Conference on Aging (Reel 3, Frame 150)
      - Regional Conference on Aging (Reel 3, Frame 165)
      - Pensions and Social Security (Reel 3, Frame 180)
      - Tax Exemption (Reel 3, Frame 221)
      - General (Reel 4, Frame 4)
  - Agriculture (Reel 4)
    - Animal Industry (Reel 4)
      - Humane Slaughter (Reel 4, Frame 34)
        - Dogs (Reel 4, Frame 39)
    - Agriculture & Markets (Reel 4)
      - Fairs (Reel 4, Frame 50)
      - Department of Food Control (Reel 4, Frame 71)
    - Products (Reel 4)
      - Grapes (Reel 4, Frame 86)
      - Milk (Reel 4, Frame 95)
      - Milk Marketing (Reel 4, Frame 107)
      - Apples (Reel 4, Frame 124)
    - Agriculture & Markets, Department of (Reel 4, Frame 127)
    - General (Reel 4, Frame 138)
  - Authorities and Commissions (Reel 4, Reel 5, Reel 7, Reel 6)
    - Adirondack Mountain Authority (Reel 4, Frame 163)
    - Albany Port District Commission (Reel 4, Frame 170)
    - New York State Atomic & Space Development Authority (Reel 4, Frame 173)
    - New York State Bridge Authority (Reel 4, Frame 241)
    - Temporary State Commission on the Capital City (Reel 4, Frame 247)
    - Delaware River Basin Commission, 1966 June-December (Reel 4, Frame 253)
    - Delaware River Basin Commission, 1963 January-1966 July (Reel 5, Frame 4)
    - State Dormitory Authority (Reel 5, Frame 23)
    - East Hudson River Parkway Authority (Reel 5, Frame 29)
    - Hudson River Valley Commission New (Reel 5, Frame 38)
    - York Job Development Authority (Reel 5, Frame 81)
    - Jones Beach State Parkway Authority (Reel 5, Frame 109)
    - State Liquor Authority (Reel 5, Frame 110)
    - Temporary State Commission on Low-Income Housing (Reel 5, Frame 156)
    - Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Fund, 1965-1966 (Reel 5, Frame 169)
    - Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Fund, 1963-1965 (Reel 6, Frame 5)
    - New York City Housing Authority (Reel 6, Frame 56)
    - New York City Transit Authority (Reel 6, Frame 60)
    - Niagara Frontier Port Authority (Reel 6, Frame 79)
    - Ogdensburg Bridge & Port Authority (Reel 6, Frame 122)
    - Temporary State Commission on Per Capita Aid (Reel 6, Frame 130)
    - Port of New York Authority (Reel 6, Frame 131)
    - Power Authority of New York State, 1965 November-1966 (Reel 6, Frame 247)
    - Power Authority of New York State (Reel 7)
      - 1963 January-1965 October (Reel 7, Frame 4)
    - Port of Oswego Authority (Reel 7, Frame 24)
    - Temporary State Commission to Study Rents and Rental Conditions (Reel 7, Frame 26)
    - Commission on Revision of the Penal Law and Criminal Code (Reel 7, Frame 30)
    - New York State Science & Technology Foundation (Reel 7, Frame 47)
    - Thousand Island Bridge Authority (Reel 7, Frame 77)
    - New York State Thruway Authority (Reel 7, Frame 79)
    - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Reel 7, Frame 109)
    - Waterfront Commission (Reel 7, Frame 125)
    - White Plains Parking Authority (Reel 7, Frame 144)
      - A-Z (Reel 7, Frame 146)
      - General (Reel 7, Frame 216)
  - Banking (Reel 7, Reel 8)
    - Banking, Department of (Reel 7, Frame 217)
    - Banks: General, 1966 (Reel 7, Frame 233)
    - Banks: General, 1963-1966 (Reel 8, Frame 5)
  - Civil Defense (Reel 8)
    - Federal (Reel 8, Frame 16)
      - National Plan (Reel 8, Frame 19)
    - New York State Civil Defense Commission (Reel 8, Frame 22)
    - State Defense Council (Reel 8, Frame 44)
    - General (Reel 8, Frame 46)
  - Commemorative Observances (Reel 8, Reel 9)
    - Captive Nations Week (Reel 8, Frame 91)
    - Columbus Day (Reel 8, Frame 93)
    - United Nations Day (Reel 8, Frame 113)
    - A-Poe (Reel 8, Frame 118)
    - Pol-Z (Reel 9, Frame 5)
  - Commerce (Reel 9, Reel 10, Reel 11, Reel 12, Reel 13)
    - General (Reel 9)
      - Economic Development (Reel 9, Frame 59)
    - Aviation (Reel 9)
      - General (Reel 9, Frame 60)
      - Airports (Reel 9, Frame 62)
      - General (Reel 9, Frame 104)
        - Business Promotion (Reel 9, Frame 110)
        - Business Promotion Convention (Reel 9, Frame 136)
        - Business Promotion General (Reel 9)
          - 1963 July-1966 December (Reel 9, Frame 182)
    - Business (Reel 10)
      - Promotion (Reel 10)
        - General, 1963 January-July (Reel 10, Frame 3)
      - Publicity (Reel 10, Frame 13)
      - Research (Reel 10, Frame 30)
      - Service (Reel 10, Frame 51)
    - Radio, TV & Motion Pictures (Reel 10, Reel 11)
      - Schedules & Transcripts (Reel 10, Frame 51)
        - Executive Chamber (Reel 10, Frame 95)
        - "Meet the Press" (Reel 10, Frame 169)
        - General, 1963 February-1966 (Reel 10, Frame 175)
        - General, 1963 January-February (Reel 11, Frame 5)
    - Travel (Reel 11, Frame 11)
    - Womens Program, Department of (Reel 11, Frame 27)
    - General (Reel 11, Reel 12, Reel 13)
      - World's Fair (Reel 11, Frame 117)
      - Washington Office
        - 1966 April-December (Reel 11, Frame 245)
        - 1963 January-1966 April (Reel 12, Frame 12)
      - A-Z (Reel 12, Frame 142)
      - 1966 February-December (Reel 12, Frame 243)
      - 1963 January-1966 March (Reel 13, Frame 12)
  - Conservation (Reel 13, Reel 14)
    - Fish and Game (Reel 13, Frame 63)
      - General, 1963-1966 (Reel 13, Frame 83)
    - Lands & Forests (Reel 13, Frame 106)
      - General, 1965 August-1966 December (Reel 13, Frame 178)
    - General, 1963 January-1965 July (Reel 14, Frame 4)
    - Letters of Commendation (Reel 14, Frame 44)
    - Department of (Reel 14)
      - General (Reel 14, Frame 47)
  - Consumer (Reel 14)
    - Consumer, Problems of (Reel 14, Frame 136)
  - Correction (Reel 14, Reel 15)
    - Department of (Reel 14, Frame 172)
    - Parole (Reel 14)
      - Department of (Reel 14, Frame 175)
    - General (Reel 14, Frame 191)
    - Parole (Reel 14)
      - Division of (Reel 14, Frame 201)
      - General (Reel 14, Frame 211)
    - Institutions (Reel 15)
      - Inspection Reports (Reel 15, Frame 9)
        - Dannemora (Reel 15, Frame 35)
        - Mattewan (Reel 15, Frame 43)
        - A-Z (Reel 15, Frame 59)
        - General (Reel 15, Frame 110)
  - Disaster (Reel 15, Reel 16)
    - Drought (Reel 15, Frame 162)
    - Others (Reel 15, Frame 194)
    - Federal-State Disaster Agreement (Reel 15, Frame 232)
    - Floods (Reel 15, Reel 16)
      - Flood Control (Reel 15, Frame 238)
      - Erie County, 1963 August-September (Reel 15, Frame 246)
      - Erie County, 1963 August-1966 (Reel 16, Frame 2)
      - Flood Control (Reel 16)
        - Long Island Sound (Reel 16, Frame 14)
      - General (Reel 16, Frame 37)
  - Discrimination (Reel 16, Reel 17)
    - Human Rights Commission (Reel 16, Frame 57)
    - Civil Rights (Reel 16, Frame 103)
      - Racial Intolerance (Reel 16, Frame 107)
      - Civil Rights & Race Relations (Reel 16, Frame 175)
      - Racial Imbalance (Reel 16, Frame 195)
      - State Commission on Education
        - 1963 July-1966 (Reel 16, Frame 220)
        - 1963 January-July (Reel 17, Frame 2)
      - Special Cabinet Committee on Civil Rights (Reel 17, Frame 12)
        - March on Washington (Reel 17, Frame 14)
        - Race Relations (Harlem) (Reel 17, Frame 15)
        - Race Imbalance (New York City) (Reel 17, Frame 20)
        - Race Relations (Reel 17, Frame 54)
        - General (Reel 17, Frame 63)
  - Employment (Reel 17)
    - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 17, Frame 164)
    - Departments (Reel 17, Frame 170)
      - Roohdale Housing Project (Reel 17, Frame 178)
        - General (Reel 17, Frame 183)
  - Housing (Reel 17, Reel 18)
    - General
      - 1966 March-December (Reel 17, Frame 245)
      - 1963 January-1966 February (Reel 18, Frame 3)
  - Education
    - Department of (Reel 18, Frame 32)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation (Reel 18, Frame 73)
    - Department of (Reel 18)
      - Board of Regents (Reel 18, Frame 102)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 18, Frame 109)
      - General (Reel 18, Frame 124)
    - Finances (Reel 20, Frame 79)
      - State Aid (Reel 20, Frame 114)
    - Museums & Historical Sites (Reel 20, Reel 21)
      - A-H (Reel 20, Frame 237)
      - H-Z (Reel 21, Frame 7)
      - General (Reel 21, Frame 161)
    - Schools (Reel 21, Reel 22, Reel 23, Reel 24)
      - High & Elementary (Reel 21)
        - A-Z (Reel 21, Frame 168)
      - Colleges (Reel 21, Reel 22, Reel 23, Reel 24)
        - Alfred
          - 1964 February-1966 (Reel 21, Frame 243)
          - 1963 May-1964 February (Reel 22, Frame 2)
        - SUNY Buffalo (Reel 22, Frame 5)
        - University of California (Reel 22, Frame 32)
        - City University (Reel 22, Frame 36)
        - Cornell University (Reel 22, Frame 74)
        - Dartmouth College (Reel 22, Frame 174)
        - Dutchess Community College (Reel 22, Frame 178)
        - Harvard (Reel 22, Frame 186)
        - Long Island General (Reel 22, Frame 188)
        - Marymount College (Reel 22, Frame 209)
        - New York University (Reel 22, Frame 212)
        - Northwestern University (Reel 22, Frame 222)
        - Pace College (Reel 22, Frame 224)
        - St. Johns University (Reel 22, Frame 225)
        - Science Centers (Reel 22, Frame 228)
        - Science Centers (Reel 23, Frame 4)
        - Syracuse University (Reel 23, Frame 37)
        - U.S. Military Academy (Reel 23, Frame 69)
        - Union College (Reel 23, Frame 72)
        - A-Sa (Reel 23, Frame 76)
        - Sc-Z (Reel 24, Frame 5)
        - General (Reel 24, Frame 41)
    - State University (Reel 24, Reel 25, Reel 26)
      - Board of Trustees (Reel 24, Frame 86)
      - Community Colleges Proposal (Reel 24, Frame 86)
      - Construction Fund (Reel 24, Frame 90)
      - Proposed Colleges (Reel 24, Frame 163)
      - Scholarships (Reel 24, Frame 193)
      - Translation
        - 1966 September-December (Reel 24, Frame 244)
        - 1966 February-August (Reel 25, Frame 4)
      - General (Reel 25, Frame 24)
        - Arts (Reel 25, Frame 144)
          - Arts Council (Reel 25, Frame 160)
          - General (Reel 25, Frame 197)
      - Adult Education (Reel 25, Frame 243)
      - Educational Television
        - 1966 February-December (Reel 25, Frame 248)
        - 1963 February-1966 February (Reel 26, Frame 7)
    - Higher Education (Reel 26, Reel 27)
      - Medical Education (Reel 26, Frame 36)
      - Proposed Colleges (Reel 26, Frame 106)
      - Scholarship Incentive Award (Reel 26, Frame 142)
      - Tuition (Reel 26, Frame 184)
      - Tuition (Reel 27, Frame 8)
      - Westchester County Facilities (Reel 27, Frame 55)
      - General (Reel 27, Frame 68)
    - Libraries (Reel 27, Reel 28)
      - A-Z (Reel 27, Frame 170)
      - General (Reel 27, Frame 195)
      - Library Conferences
        - 1963 June-1966 December (Reel 27, Frame 200)
        - 1963 January-June (Reel 28, Frame 4)
    - Local Problems (Reel 28, Frame 18)
    - General (Reel 28, Reel 29)
      - Retarded and Handicapped Children (Reel 28, Frame 98)
      - Local Problems (Reel 28, Frame 123)
      - School Buses (Reel 28, Frame 134)
      - Students in Politics (Reel 28, Frame 137)
      - Textbook Law (Reel 28, Frame 147)
      - 1964 June-1966 December (Reel 28, Frame 164)
      - 1963 January-1964 May (Reel 29, Frame 7)
  - Executive Clemency (Reel 29, Reel 30)
    - 1965 September 13-1966 December (Reel 29, Frame 45)
    - 1963 January-1965 September 10 (Reel 30, Frame 3)
  - Extradition (Reel 30)
    - Extradition, 1963-1966 (Reel 30, Frame 109)
  - Fiscal (Reel 30, Reel 31, Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35)
    - Audit & Control (Reel 30, Reel 31)
      - 1965 November-1966 December (Reel 30, Frame 126)
      - 1965 October-November (Reel 31, Frame 5)
    - Accounting & Auditing (Reel 31, Frame 17)
      Scope and Contents note
      including audit reports and papers from the Department of Audit Control.
    - Yearly Budget (Reel 31, Reel 32)
      - 1966 April-December (Reel 31, Frame 230)
      - 1963 January-1965 April (Reel 32, Frame 9)
    - Budget, Division of (Reel 32, Frame 89)
    - Budget Summary (Reel 32, Frame 116)
    - Annual Message (Reel 32, Frame 131)
    - Expenditures (Reel 32)
      - Office of General Services (Reel 32)
        - Standards & Purchases (Reel 32, Frame 142)
        - Central Operations (Reel 32, Frame 195)
        - Real Property Management (Reel 32, Frame 198)
        - State Cars (Reel 32, Frame 210)
        - General (Reel 32, Frame 217)
      - General (Reel 32, Frame 234)
    - Revenues (Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35)
      - Fees (Reel 32)
        - Liquor (Reel 32, Frame 238)
          - General
            - 1963 March-1966 December (Reel 32, Frame 245)
            - 1963 January-March (Reel 33, Frame 2)
      - Motor Vehicle Department (Reel 33)
        - Compulsory Auto Inspection (Reel 33, Frame 14)
        - Registration (Reel 33, Frame 20)
        - Fees (Reel 33, Frame 46)
        - License Plates (Reel 33)
          - Special (Reel 33, Frame 81)
          - General (Reel 33, Frame 90)
        - Operators Licenses (Reel 33, Frame 116)
        - Letters of Commendation (Reel 33, Frame 174)
        - General (Reel 33, Frame 179)
      - Tax & Finances (Reel 33)
        - Department of (Reel 33, Frame 192)
        - Income Tax Return (Reel 33, Frame 210)
        - Income Tax Bureau (Reel 33, Frame 224)
      - Taxation
        - Cigarette Tax (Reel 33, Frame 229)
        - Governor's Program (Reel 33, Frame 237)
        - Income Tax (Reel 34)
          - General (Reel 34, Frame 2)
        - Lottery (Reel 34, Frame 19)
        - New York City Taxes (Reel 34, Frame 88)
        - Off-Track Betting (Reel 34, Frame 179)
        - Property Tax (Reel 34, Frame 217)
        - Sales Tax
          - 1966 March-December (Reel 34, Frame 240)
          - 1963 January-1966 January (Reel 35, Frame 2)
        - Stock Transfer Tax (Reel 35, Frame 85)
        - Tolls (Reel 35, Frame 90)
        - General (Reel 35, Frame 111)
  - Fund Raising (Reel 35)
    - Fund Raising Campaign (Reel 35)
      - Albany Red Cross (Reel 35, Frame 184)
      - Cancer Society (Reel 35, Frame 191)
      - Community Chest Red Cross (Reel 35, Frame 196)
      - Cerebral Palsy (Reel 35, Frame 197)
      - Cystic Fibrosis (Reel 35, Frame 198)
      - Greater New York Fund (Reel 35, Frame 200)
      - Heart Fund (Reel 35, Frame 207)
      - Welfare Fund (Reel 35, Frame 210)
      - Leukemia Fund (Reel 35, Frame 212)
      - Mental Health Fund (Reel 35, Frame 213)
      - Muscular Dystrophy (Reel 35, Frame 215)
      - A-Z (Reel 35, Frame 217)
  - Government (Reel 35, Reel 36, Reel 37, Reel 38, Reel 39, Reel 40, Reel 41, Reel 42, Reel 43, Reel 44)
    - Federal (Reel 35, Reel 36, Reel 37)
      - Department of Agriculture (Reel 35, Frame 225)
      - Appalachian Regional Development (Reel 35, Frame 228)
      - Department of Commerce
        - 1966 (Reel 35, Frame 245)
        - 1963-1966 (Reel 36, Frame 3)
      - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Reel 36, Frame 20)
      - Inauguration (Reel 36, Frame 33)
      - U.S. Department of the Interior (Reel 36, Frame 35)
      - Internal Revenue Service (Reel 36, Frame 43)
      - Department of Labor (Reel 36, Frame 46)
      - Economic Opportunity Act (Reel 36, Frame 70)
      - JFK Memorial
        - 1963 December-1966 December (Reel 36, Frame 182)
        - 1963 November-December (Reel 37, Frame 30)
      - Post Office Department (Reel 37, Frame 33)
      - Federal Budget (Reel 37, Frame 49)
      - Treasury Department (Reel 37, Frame 54)
      - U.S. Atomic Energy Commission (Reel 37, Frame 60)
      - Veterans Administration (Reel 37, Frame 65)
      - A-Z (Reel 37, Frame 99)
      - General (Reel 37, Frame 133)
    - International (Reel 37, Reel 38, Reel 39)
      - Afghanistan (Reel 37, Frame 206)
      - Argentina (Reel 37, Frame 210)
      - Saudi Arabia (Reel 37, Frame 213)
      - Australia (Reel 37, Frame 230)
      - Austria (Reel 37, Frame 232)
      - Belgium (Reel 37, Frame 233)
      - Bolivia (Reel 37, Frame 238)
      - Brazil (Reel 37, Frame 240)
      - Canada (Reel 37, Frame 245)
      - Chile (Reel 37, Frame 256)
      - China (Reel 37, Frame 258)
      - Costa Rica (Reel 37, Frame 260)
      - Cuba
        - 1963-1966 (Reel 37, Frame 263)
        - 1963 (Reel 38, Frame 8)
      - Dominican Republic (Reel 38, Frame 19)
      - France (Reel 38, Frame 23)
      - Germany (Reel 38, Frame 28)
      - Ghana (Reel 38, Frame 35)
      - Guatemala (Reel 38, Frame 36)
      - India (Reel 38, Frame 37)
      - Indonesia (Reel 38, Frame 53)
      - Israel (Reel 38, Frame 57)
      - Italy (Reel 38, Frame 59)
      - Japan (Reel 38, Frame 66)
      - Jordan (Reel 38, Frame 71)
      - Kuwait (Reel 38, Frame 72)
      - Latin America (Reel 38, Frame 73)
      - Mexico (Reel 38, Frame 88)
      - Morocco (Reel 38, Frame 92)
      - Nepal (Reel 38, Frame 93)
      - Nicaragua (Reel 38, Frame 95)
      - Norway (Reel 38, Frame 97)
      - Pakistan (Reel 38, Frame 99)
      - Peru (Reel 38, Frame 106)
      - Puerto Rico (Reel 38, Frame 107)
      - Somalia (Reel 38, Frame 111)
      - South and North Vietnam (Reel 38, Frame 112)
      - Spain (Reel 38, Frame 141)
      - Sweden (Reel 38, Frame 145)
      - Switzerland (Reel 38, Frame 149)
      - United Nations (Reel 38, Frame 150)
      - Venezuela (Reel 38, Frame 161)
      - Yugoslavia (Reel 38, Frame 173)
      - A-S (Reel 38, Frame 176)
      - T-Z (Reel 39, Frame 17)
      - International Official Visitors (Reel 39, Frame 30)
      - General (Reel 39, Frame 41)
    - City (Reel 39, Reel 40)
      - Albany (Reel 39)
        - South Mall (Reel 39, Frame 46)
        - General (Reel 39, Frame 80)
      - Amsterdam (Reel 39, Frame 91)
      - Buffalo (Reel 39, Frame 95)
      - Elmira (Reel 39, Frame 107)
      - Mount Vernon (Reel 39, Frame 110)
      - Newburgh (Reel 39, Frame 116)
      - New Rochelle (Reel 39, Frame 118)
      - New York City
        - 1964 July-1966 December (Reel 39, Frame 122)
        - 1963 January-December (Reel 40, Frame 7)
      - Niagara Falls (Reel 40, Frame 27)
      - Rochester (Reel 40, Frame 37)
      - Rome (Reel 40, Frame 39)
      - Rye (Reel 40, Frame 41)
      - Syracuse (Reel 40, Frame 42)
      - Troy (Reel 40, Frame 53)
      - Utica (Reel 40, Frame 57)
      - A-Z (Reel 40, Frame 59)
    - County (Reel 40, Reel 41, Reel 42)
      - Albany (Reel 40, Frame 116)
      - Allegany (Reel 40, Frame 121)
      - Bronx (Reel 40, Frame 124)
      - Broome (Reel 40, Frame 140)
      - Chautauqua (Reel 40, Frame 146)
      - Chemung (Reel 40, Frame 157)
      - Clinton (Reel 40, Frame 161)
      - Delaware (Reel 40, Frame 164)
      - Dutchess (Reel 40, Frame 168)
      - Erie (Reel 40, Frame 175)
      - Essex (Reel 40, Frame 192)
      - Fulton (Reel 40, Frame 194)
      - Genesee (Reel 40, Frame 197)
      - Greene (Reel 40, Frame 198)
      - Hamilton (Reel 40, Frame 206)
      - Herkimer (Reel 40, Frame 208)
      - Kings (Reel 40, Frame 211)
      - Livingston (Reel 40, Frame 237)
      - Monroe (Reel 40, Frame 238)
      - Monroe (Reel 41, Frame 2)
      - Nassau (Reel 41, Frame 4)
      - New York (Reel 41, Frame 58)
      - Niagara (Reel 41, Frame 88)
      - Oneida (Reel 41, Frame 97)
      - Onondaga (Reel 41, Frame 110)
      - Orange (Reel 41, Frame 123)
      - Putnam (Reel 41, Frame 129)
      - Queens (Reel 41, Frame 137)
      - Richmond (Reel 41, Frame 168)
      - Rockland (Reel 41, Frame 174)
      - St. Lawrence (Reel 41, Frame 189)
      - Saratoga (Reel 41, Frame 199)
      - Schenectady (Reel 41, Frame 204)
      - Seneca (Reel 41, Frame 216)
      - Steuben (Reel 41, Frame 222)
      - Suffolk
        - 1966 (Reel 41, Frame 228)
        - 1963-1965 (Reel 42, Frame 3)
      - Sullivan (Reel 42, Frame 42)
      - Tompkins (Reel 42, Frame 65)
      - Ulster (Reel 42, Frame 74)
      - Warren (Reel 42, Frame 79)
      - Westchester (Reel 42, Frame 84)
      - A-Z (Reel 42, Frame 128)